Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Sweet Secrets=
=أسرار حلوة=
=Episode 16= (The Nine Soul Bridge)
=الحلقة 16= (جسر النفوس التسعة)
What's wrong, Li Motong?
ما الأمر يا لي موتونغ؟
Are you cold?
هل انت بارد؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You wouldn't be suffering like this
لن تعاني مثل هذا
if it weren't for me.
لو لم يكن الأمر لي.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
I should've trusted you.
كان ينبغي لي أن أثق بك.
I should've loved you.
كان ينبغي لي أن أحبك.
You Zimei.
أنت زيمي.
You Zimei must have a way.
يجب أن يكون لديك طريقة يا زيمي.
Wait here.
انتظر هنا.
I'll be back.
سأعود.
Don't go…
لا تذهب…
Yan…
أولئك…
Miss You!
أفتقدك!
He's wracked with agonizing pain from the Mei pearl's recoil.
لقد أصيب بألم مبرح بسبب ارتداد لؤلؤة مي.
Miss You!
أفتقدك!
Can you save him? Please!
هل يمكنك إنقاذه؟ من فضلك!
You Zimei!
أنت زيمي!
How's Li Motong?
كيف حال لي موتونغ؟
He…
هو…
he's hurting badly.
إنه يتألم بشدة.
Please, I'm begging you, save him.
من فضلك، أنا أتوسل إليك، أنقذه.
You don't blame me?
لا تلومني؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
Just save him.
فقط انقذه .
Please save him.
من فضلك انقذه.
There is a way,
هناك طريقة
but you'll have to go
ولكن عليك أن تذهب
to an extremely dangerous place.
إلى مكان خطير للغاية.
Will you
سوف تفعل
go there?
اذهب هناك؟
I will.
أنا سوف.
If it means saving him,
إذا كان ذلك يعني إنقاذه،
I'll go through blades and fire,
سأذهب من خلال الشفرات والنار،
thunder and storms,
الرعد والعواصف،
even down to the deepest abyss.
حتى أعمق الهاوية.
I've restored the dream disc.
لقد قمت باستعادة قرص الحلم.
Inside the dream realm, there's a thousand-year-old Bodhi Tree.
داخل عالم الأحلام، هناك شجرة بودي عمرها ألف عام.
Its Bodhi Fruit can ease the suffering of the afflicted heart.
يمكن لفاكهة بودي أن تخفف من معاناة القلب المنكوب.
Miss Lu,
الآنسة لو،
if you will risk everything for him,
إذا كنت ستخاطر بكل شيء من أجله،
follow me
اتبعني
into the dream disc.
في قرص الحلم.
Once inside the dream realm,
بمجرد دخولك إلى عالم الأحلام،
you must cross the Nine Soul Bridge
يجب عليك عبور جسر النفوس التسعة
to obtain the Bodhi Fruit.
للحصول على فاكهة بودي.
On that bridge,
على هذا الجسر،
all your past and present lives will be revealed.
سيتم الكشف عن كل حياتك الماضية والحالية .
If your soul falters while crossing,
إذا تعثرت روحك أثناء العبور،
you'll be consumed
سوف يتم استهلاكك
by agony beyond bearing.
بسبب الألم الذي لا يطاق.
You're mortal
أنت بشري
and already wounded all over.
وجريح بالفعل في كل مكان.
Lu Huayan,
لو هوايان,
are you sure
هل أنت متأكد؟
you want to cross the bridge?
هل تريد عبور الجسر؟
I will.
أنا سوف.
I'll get the Bodhi Fruit.
سأحصل على فاكهة بودي.
I'll save him.
سأنقذه.
Lu Huayan,
لو هوايان,
you think you can cross the Nine Soul Bridge?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع عبور جسر النفوس التسعة؟
Those who defy fate will have their souls torn apart.
أولئك الذين يتحدون القدر سوف يتم تمزيق أرواحهم.
Go back to the Mortal Realm while you still can.
عد إلى عالم البشر بينما لا يزال بإمكانك ذلك.
If you keep going,
إذا واصلت،
you won't just fail to save him.
لن تفشل في إنقاذه.
You'll destroy yourself too.
سوف تدمر نفسك أيضًا
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You won't challenge my resolve.
لن تتحدى قراري.
I will cross this bridge.
سأعبر هذا الجسر.
I will save Li Motong!
سأنقذ لي موتونغ!
Have you forgotten your sister's tragic death?
هل نسيت موت أختك المأساوي؟
She died so horribly,
لقد ماتت بشكل فظيع،
yet you're the one who lived.
ولكنك أنت الذي عشت.
Why was it you who survived,
لماذا كنت أنت الذي نجوت؟
and not her?
وليس هي؟
(Lu Huayan,)
(لو هوايان،)
(may you face your heart's trial)
(أرجو أن تواجه اختبار قلبك)
(and cross the Nine Soul Bridge.)
(وعبور جسر النفوس التسعة.)
Yan.
نعم.
Sister,
أخت،
is it you?
هل هو انت؟
Yan,
نعم،
ignore those treacherous voices.
تجاهل تلك الأصوات الخائنة.
I've met an unfortunate end,
لقد واجهت نهاية مؤسفة،
but it wasn't by your hand.
ولكن لم يكن ذلك بيدك.
You shouldn't blame yourself,
لا يجب عليك أن تلوم نفسك،
or drown in guilt because of me.
أو تغرق في الشعور بالذنب بسببي.
It was my fault.
كانت غلطتي.
It's my fault,
إنه خطئي
Sister.
أخت.
If I hadn't been weak and useless,
لو لم أكن ضعيفًا وعديم الفائدة،
if I could've protected you,
لو كان بإمكاني حمايتك،
you wouldn't have died.
لم تكن لتموت.
It should've been me.
كان ينبغي أن أكون أنا.
Not you.
ليس انت.
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
You already did everything you could
لقد فعلت كل ما بوسعك بالفعل
to protect me.
لحمايتي.
We grew up together. We relied on each other for everything.
كبرنا معًا، واعتمدنا على بعضنا البعض في كل شيء.
The joy,
الفرحة
companionship,
الرفقة،
and protection you gave me
والحماية التي قدمتها لي
can't be measured in time.
لا يمكن قياسها بالوقت.
The fact that you exist in this world,
حقيقة أنك موجود في هذا العالم،
that you became my sister,
أنك أصبحت أختي،
is already the greatest gift you could give me.
إنها بالفعل أعظم هدية يمكنك أن تقدمها لي.
Sister,
أخت،
do you really
هل انت حقا
mean it?
هل تقصد ذلك؟
Yan,
نعم،
I want you to live on.
أريدك أن تعيش.
If you want me to rest in peace,
إذا كنت تريدني أن أرتاح بسلام،
promise me
وعدني
you'll step out of the shadows of the past.
سوف تخرج من ظلال الماضي.
Yan,
نعم،
live on.
استمر في العيش.
Sister,
أخت،
I miss you…
أفتقدك…
Sister!
أخت!
Sister…
أخت…
I will live.
سوف أعيش.
I'll live well, for you.
سأعيش جيدا من أجلك.
I can do it.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
(I can save you.)
(أستطيع أن أنقذك.)
Sister,
أخت،
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪